Finding Aid for Netzorg family papers, late 1800s-2012.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Morton J. and Petra Fuld Netzorg papers
  - Correspondence
    - McChesney, Mary L., 1983 (Box 16)
    - McCoy, Alfred W., 1978-1983 (Box 16)
    - McDaniel, Mary, 1977-1985 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - McFadden, Dorothy L., 1951 (Box 16)
    - McHale, Thomas, 1956-1962 (Box 16)
    - McLean, K. Peter, 1969 (Box 16)
    - McLennan, Marshall S., 1973 (Box 16)
    - Meggitt, Mervyn, 1962-1963 (Box 16)
    - Meinrath, Jutta with gaps, 1940-1987; 4 folders (Box 16)
    - Mellin, Corinne, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Mendoza, Helen, 1983-1986; 1989 (Box 16)
    - Menkes, Josh and Aviva, 1952 (Box 16)
    - Merhab, William, 1978 (Box 16)
    - Merkle, J.W., 1949 (Box 16)
    - Merlander, Kurt with gaps, 1948-1977; 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Merriman, Hiram, 1965 (Box 16)
    - Merritt, Lucia, 1956-1999 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Metro Detroit Book & Author Society, 9, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
    - Meyer, Julia, 1983-1986 (Box 16)
    - Miailhe, W. A. Burke, 1956 (Box 16)
    - Michigan, University of
      - Association for Asian Studies, 1957-1977 (with gaps) (Box 16)
      - Center for South and Southeast Asian Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 16)
    - Migron, Saul, 1970-1990 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Miller, Henry L. (Hank), 1963-1987 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Miller, Kitty, 1986-1987 (Box 16)
    - Miller, Robert, 1929; 1986; undated (Box 16)
    - Miller, Sarah, 1940-1941 (Box 16)
    - Milne, Lucie A., 1993-1996; 2002 (Box 16)
    - Miner, Horace M., 1968 (Box 16)
    - Miranda, Luis G., 1956-1967; 1970; 4 folders (Box 16)
    - Mittelberger, Frank and Marianne, 1945 (Box 16)
    - Mock, Charmian, undated (Box 16)
    - Modern Book Company, 1970 (Box 16)
    - Mojares, Resil B., 1978-1987 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Molony, Carol H., 1971 (Box 16)
    - Monroe, Helen, 1949-1953 (Box 16)
    - Montemayor, Jesus M., 1960-1961 (Box 16)
    - Montgomery, Elizabeth, 1980 (Box 16)
    - Montilla, Alberto, 1975-1986 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Moody, Samuel B., 1971; 1982 (Box 16)
    - Moser, Mrs., 1946 (Box 16)
    - Moses, James R., 1975 (Box 16)
    - Mueller, Robert, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
    - Mullen, Yvonne, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Munger, Edwin S., 1962-1963; 1971 (Box 16)
    - Murphy, Irene, 1973-1987 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Murray, Charlotte, 1959-1962 (with gaps) (Box 16)
    - Murumbi, Joseph, 1962-1963; 1967 (Box 16)
    - Musgrave, John, 1964-1975 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Muskin, Laurie, 1967-1968 (Box 16)
    - Nagao, Philip M., 1987 (Box 16)
    - Naiman, Sandra, 1986 (Box 16)
    - Nairn, Ronald, 1968-1974 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - National Stamp Collectors, 1956 (Box 16)
    - Nehaus, Marjorie, 1984 (Box 16)
    - Nelson, Frances Russell, 1978-1991 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Nemenzo, Catalina A., 1975-1976 (Box 16)
    - Nerbonne, Joseph J., 1972-1973 (Box 16)
    - Nestle, Mark and Emily, 1943-1963 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Nestler, Harold, 1970-1972 (Box 16)
    - Nethercott, Thomas and Eva, 1962-1986 (scattered) (Box 16)
    - Netzorg family, 1944-1993; 17 folders (Box 17)
    - Newberg, Walter, 1963 (Box 17)
    - New Day Publishing, 1970-1971 (Box 17)
    - New York State Education Department, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
    - Nicanor, Precioso M. and1987, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Nichols, Michael, 1969-1990 (scattered) (Box 17)
    - Nicksic, Katherine, 1962; 1964 (Box 17)
    - Nielsen, C. M., 1980-1995 (scattered) (Box 17)
    - Nielsen, L. R., 1946 (Box 17)
    - Nigerian Book Suppliers, 1968-1969; 1971 (Box 17)
    - Norling, Bernard, 1983-1987 (Box 17)
    - Nwankwo-Ifejika & Co., 1971 (Box 17)
    - Nyack Missionary College, 1971 (Box 17)
    - Nyland, Fritz C., 1969-1973 (Box 17)
    - O’Brien, James, 1966-1987 (scattered) (Box 17)
    - O’Brien, Kiaran (Fontanella), 1968; undated (Box 17)
    - O’Brien, Rose, 1971; 1974; undated (Box 17)
    - O’Day, Ray M., 1956; 1964-1965 (Box 17)
    - Odom, William, 1980-1984 (Box 17)
    - Ogiwara, Hiroaki, 1977-1978 (Box 17)
    - Ohio State University, 1975 (Box 17)
    - Oliphant, Richard, 1956 (Box 17)
    - Oliven, Jutta V., 1951; 1967 (Box 17)
    - Olson, John E., 1985; 1987 (Box 17)
    - Onorato, Michael P. with gaps, 1967-2001; 5 folders (Box 17)
    - Orendain, Joan, 1982-1988 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Ortiz, Pacifico, 1961; 1965-1966 (Box 18)
    - Osborne, Shirley, 1967-1980 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Ouye, Walter, 1976 (Box 18)
    - Overton, Leonard C., 1959-1960 (Box 18)
    - Owen, Norman G., 1977-2002 (with gaps) (Box 18)
    - Ozan, Terry and Martin, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
    - Pacheco, Esther, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Pacific Affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 18)
    - Pacific Book Supply Co., 1956 (Box 18)
    - Padua, Amando A., 1974-1976 (Box 18)
    - Pagley, Daniel, 1956-1974 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Pagulong, Clarita., 1986-1987; 1995-1996 (Box 18)
    - Palmer, Carlos and Emily, 1947 (Box 18)
    - Palmeri, Tom and Diane
      - Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 18)
      - Family to family 1977-2002 with gaps and undated, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Palmquist, Dennis and Elizabeth, 1961-1980 (scattered); undated (Box 18)
    - Panlilio, Yay, 1945; 1976-1978 (Box 18)
    - Parkins, Maurice, 1981-1982 (Box 18)
    - Parr, Joseph, 1969-1996 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Parsons, Peter, 1999-2000 (Box 18)
    - Patience, Ellen, 1977; 1981 (Box 18)
    - Patterson, John A., 1975-1998 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Payne, John R., 1971-1972 (Box 18)
    - Payton, Margaret, 1949-1950 (Box 18)
    - Pearl, Nancy, 1961-1987 (with gaps) (Box 18)
    - Peattie, Mark R., 1990 (Box 18)
    - Pecson, Geronima T., 1957-1958 (Box 18)
    - Pedersen, Paul, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
    - Pelzer, Karl, 1996; 1973 (Box 18)
    - Peñaranda, Oscar, 1973 (Box 18)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1970-1971; 1974 (Box 18)
    - Perez, Gilbert, 1956 (Box 18)
    - Perkins Oriental Books, 1961-1962 (Box 18)
    - Philippine-American Association, 1967 (Box 18)
    - Philippine Art Gallery, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Philippine Association, 1956 (Box 18)
    - Philippine Consulate General, Chicago, IL, 1984 (Box 18)
    - Philippine Education Company, 1962; 1965-1966 (Box 18)
    - Philippine Studies, 1966 (Box 18)
    - Philippine Social Studies Council, 1977; 1979 (Box 18)
    - Philippines, University of, 1967; 1969 (Box 18)
    - Phillips, Dorothy, 1976-2002 (with gaps) (Box 18)
    - Pilling, Patricia, 1974-2002 (with gaps) (Box 18)
    - Pines, Samuel and Sylvia, 1957-1967 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Piñon, Remedios, 1961-1985 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Player, Ian, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Plott, John C., 1970-1971; 1974 (Box 18)
    - Polk, Edith, 1949-2002 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Polk, Jonathan D., 1988 (Box 18)
    - Pollman, Anna, 1999-2002 (Box 18)
    - Powell, Ifor B., 1957; 1983 (Box 18)
    - Prabhu Book Service, 1972; 1975-1976 (Box 18)
    - Présence Africaine, 1972 (Box 18)
    - Preysler, Josephina with gaps, 1972-1990; 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Price, Michael, 1982-1999 (with gaps) (Box 18)
    - Prising, Robin, 1974 (Box 18)
    - Prizant, M., 1957; 1962 (Box 18)
    - Probsthain, Arthur, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
    - Punthi-Pustak, 1965; 1968 (Box 18)
    - Putnam’s Bookshop, 1975 (Box 18)
    - Qayyum, Abdul, 1968-1976; 1980 (Box 18)
    - Quetchenbach, Raymond T., 1975-1985; 1996 (Box 18)
    - Quirino, Carlos and Liesel, 1956-1987; 1997; 4 folders (Box 18)
    - Rahmann, Rudolf, 1958-1976 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Ralens, Carlotta, 1943-1944; 1946 (Box 18)
    - Ramos, Angel, 1975-1976 (Box 18)
    - Ramos, Lilia, 1976 (Box 18)
    - Ramos, Nicanor P., 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Rank, Dina, 1960-1961; 1980-1987 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Ray, Albert, 1978 (Box 18)
    - Realubit, Maria Lilia F., 1984 (Box 18)
    - Redl, Helen, 1970-1982 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Reed, Robert R., 1969-1970; 1979 (Box 18)
    - Reed, T. H., 1943-1944 (Box 18)
    - Reginer, Toni and Henri, 1958-1978 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Reid, Lawrence A., 1982-1983 (Box 18)
    - Reiner, Toni, 1962; undated (Box 18)
    - Reingold, David, 1977-1980 (Box 18)
    - Renner, Klaus, 1967-1996 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Renning, Rita Renee, 1970 (Box 18)
    - Reyes, Edmundo A., 1975 (Box 18)
    - Rice, Joseph, 1965-1967 (Box 18)
    - Rice, Maude, 1978-1987; 1991; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Richards, Peter C., 1978; 1983 (Box 18)
    - Riegle, Donald W., 1979-1985 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Riesz, June B., 1980-1985 (Box 18)
    - Rixhon, Gerard, 1971-1983 (with gaps) (Box 18)
    - Robb, Marion, 1978-1987 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Robb, Walter, 1959-1971 (scattered) (Box 18)
    - Robinove family with gaps, 1949-1998; 6 folders (Box 19)
    - Robson, R. W., 1961-1962 (Box 19)
    - Rodel, Rodis E., 1974 (Box 19)
    - Rodriguez, Ernesto, 1960; 1984-1987 (Box 19)
    - Rodriguez, Gloria, 1976-1994 (with gaps) (Box 19)
    - Rogers, Marvin, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
    - Roloff, Nan, 1978 (Box 19)
    - Ronck, Ronn, 1975 (Box 19)
    - Rosaldo, Renato, 1971-1983 (scattered) (Box 19)
    - Rose family, 1941-1981 (with gaps) (Box 19)
    - Rosen, David, 1969-1971 (Box 19)
    - Rosenberg, Edgar, 1984 (Box 19)
    - Rosmer, David L., 1987 (Box 19)
    - Rostenkowski, Dan, 1982 (Box 19)
    - Rotberg, Robert I., 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - Routt family, 1967; 1972 (Box 19)
    - Rowe, George E., 1983 (Box 19)
    - Rowe, John A., 1971 (Box 19)
    - Rowland, Paul, 1962 (Box 19)
    - Roy, K. K., 1966-1974 (scattered) (Box 19)
    - Rush, James, 1990 (Box 19)
    - Russell, Robert and Margaret, 1970-1980 (scattered); undated (Box 19)
    - Rustia, Erlinda F., 1973 (Box 19)
    - Ryan, William III, 1975 (Box 19)
    - Saalberg, Elen and James, 1962-2002 (scattered); undated (Box 19)
    - Sachs, Jochem, 1955-1971 (scattered) (Box 19)
    - Sachter, Nat and Joyce, 1943-1945 (Box 19)
    - Sagnip, Candido J., 1959-1960; 1964-1965 (Box 19)
    - Saito, Shiro, 1971-1985 (scattered) (Box 19)
    - Salamanca, 1986 (Box 19)
    - San Carlos, University of, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Sanchez, Ricardo with gaps, 1969-1980; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Sandoval, Judith Hancock, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Santo Tomas University, 1954; 1959-1960 (Box 19)
    - Santos, Benjamin and Beatriz, 1971-1984 (Box 19)
    - Savary, Gladys, 1957 (Box 19)
    - Savellano, Sylvia, 1974-1975 (Box 19)
    - Scharf, Arthur, 1987 (Box 19)
    - Schier, Samuel, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Schirmer, Bone, 1974-1975; 1978 (Box 19)
    - Schlegel, Adolph and Anna, 1984-1985; 1997 (Box 19)
    - Schlegel, Stuart, 1965-2002 (with gaps) (Box 19)
    - Schoepperle, Edna, 1956 (Box 19)
    - School of Oriental and African Studies Library (SOAS), 1975-1976 (Box 19)
    - Schreiner, Lothar, 1967 (Box 19)
    - Schreurs, P., 1984; 1988 (Box 19)
    - Schuler, Hollis, 1974 (Box 19)
    - Schultz, Helen, 1981 (Box 19)
    - Schulze Community Council, 1971-1972; 1975 (Box 19)
    - Schumacher, John N., 1974; 1977 (Box 19)
    - Schwartz, Carlotta, 1949 (Box 19)
    - Schweitzef, Margot, 1946-1964 (scattered) (Box 19)
    - Scott, Isabel, 1984-1987 (Box 19)
    - Scott, William Henry, 1965-1988; undated; 4 folders (Box 19)
    - Scribner, Ethel, 1966-1995 (scattered) (Box 19)
    - Seadler, Stephen Edward, 1963-1964; 1967 (Box 19)
    - Searl, Rita, 1948-1949 (Box 19)
    - Sebeok, Thomas A., 1956 (Box 19)
    - Segura, Manuel F., 1978; 1980 (Box 19)
    - Seligman, Erich, 1943; 1969 (Box 19)
    - Selver, Heinrich and Irma, 1947-1948 (Box 19)
    - Sepalla, Kay, 1976 (Box 19)
    - Sessler, Gela, 1956-1957; 1970-1996 (scattered); undated (Box 19)
    - Sevilla, Gloria T., 1972 (Box 19)
    - Sexton, Josephine E., 1982; 1985 (Box 19)
    - Shade, John A., 1978 (Box 19)
    - Shaw, Courtney with gaps, 1964-2002; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Shepard, Leslie, 970-1983 (scattered) (Box 19)
    - Shindler, Gerd, 1947 (Box 19)
    - Shufro, Herbert and Hilda with gaps, 1962-1986; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Shulman, Frank J. with gaps, 1977-2001; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Sicat, Loretta, 1979-1980 (Box 19)
    - Siega, Gorgonio D., 1978-1980 (Box 19)
    - Siega, M. J., 1981 (Box 19)
    - Siler, John, 1956-1958; 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Silliman, Robert, 1986 (Box 19)
    - Simke, Ernest E., 1976-1977 (Box 19)
    - Singapore, University of, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
    - Singer, Kurt, 1951-1976 (scattered) (Box 19)
    - Siy Eng Kiy, 1954-1955 (Box 19)
    - Skinner, Zoeth, 1977-1979 (Box 19)
    - Skow, B., 1957 (Box 19)
    - Slater, Richard R., 1986-1987 (Box 20)
    - Slaughter, Edward, 1974-1975 (Box 20)
    - Slonaker, John J., 1981; 1984 (Box 20)
    - Smith, Pauline and Robert Aura, 1944; 1958 (Box 20)
    - Smith, William Reed, 1961 (Box 20)
    - Solenberger, Robert B., 1964-1965 (Box 20)
    - Solheim, Wilhelm G., 1960-1986 (scattered) (Box 20)
    - Solis, Melchizedek, M., 1975 (Box 20)
    - Solyom, Garrett, 1972-1986 (scattered) (Box 20)
    - Sotelo, Mercedes R., 1986 (Box 20)
    - Spengler, William F., 1965-1967 (Box 20)
    - Stafford, Sheryl, 1975 (Box 20)
    - Stagg, Samuel B. (Samboyd), 1995 (Box 20)
    - Stallworth, Alma G., 1970-1974; 1984; 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Stanley, Jean, 1974 (Box 20)
    - Stapleton, Archie, 1966; 1968-1969 (Box 20)
    - Stapleton, Sarah, 1983 (Box 20)
    - Stark, Jean, 1982-1988 (scattered) (Box 20)
    - Steadman, Audrey, 1955 (Box 20)
    - Stearns, Irene Marron, 1990 (Box 20)
    - Steiner, Hans and Mona with gaps, 1955-1985; 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Steinlauf, Yvonne, 1963 (Box 20)
    - Stellby, Kitty A., 1986 (Box 20)
    - Stenger, Charles A., 1983 (Box 20)
    - Stern, Barbara, 1971-1984 (scattered) (Box 20)
    - Sternberg, David, 1969; 1976 (Box 20)
    - Stevens, Ellen, 1951 (Box 20)
    - Stevens, George, 1992 (Box 20)
    - Stewart, Gerald J., 1971 (Box 20)
    - Stewart, Gertrude, 1954-1991; 16 folders (Box 20)
    - Stewart, Sandra, 1967 (Box 20)
    - Stewart, Seumas, 1961-1962 (Box 20)
    - Stine family with gaps, 1943-2005; 15 folders (Box 20)
    - Storm, Nancy and Colton, 1970-1973 (Box 21)
    - Stout, Anthony, 1963-1968 (Box 21)
    - Straus, Wilma, 1911-1946 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Street Jackson, Lura with gaps, 1929-1983; 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Strouse, Norman H., 1960-1961 (Box 21)
    - Suchan, 1981 (Box 21)
    - Sugay, D. U., 1974-1975 (Box 21)
    - Summers, Helen, 1986 (Box 21)
    - Summers, Joseph, 1977-1981 (Box 21)
    - Swank, Harry and Grace, 1974; 1977 (Box 21)
    - Sy, Nita, 1961-1977 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Tabol, Edward L., undated (Box 21)
    - Tabuena, Romeo V., 1962-1997 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Tait, 1969 (Box 21)
    - Tala Publishing Services, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
    - Tan, Arme, 1984-1985; 1988 (Box 21)
    - Tan, Pablo, 1976-1977 (Box 21)
    - Tantuico, Francisco, 1965 (Box 21)
    - Tarling, Nicholas, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
    - Taruc, Luis, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Tawatao, Manuel, 1966 (Box 21)
    - Taylor, Alan R., 1967-1968 (Box 21)
    - Taylor, Grace (Ferrier), 1984 (Box 21)
    - Teeuwissen, Ray W., 1965-1973 (with gaps) (Box 21)
    - Temple Israel (Detroit, Mich.), 1948 (Box 21)
    - Teutsch family, 1949-1997 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Thibault, Ruth, 1939; 1941; undated (Box 21)
    - Thomas, Ralph B., 1972 (Box 21)
    - Timberlake, Lewis, 1977-1987 (Box 21)
    - Time Magazine, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Tolley, Kemp, 1977-1981 (Box 21)
    - Trager, Frank N., 1957-1984 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Tramp, George, 1982; 1984 (Box 21)
    - Tregonning, K. G., 1961-1964 (Box 21)
    - Tulchin, Philip E., 1973 (Box 21)
    - Turner, John R., 1970 (Box 21)
    - Tuttle, Charles E., 1975 (Box 21)
    - Ukarumpa High School, 1969 (Box 21)
    - UNESCO International Bureau of Education, 1969 (Box 21)
    - United Service Organizations, 1946 (Box 21)
    - United Society for the Propagation of the Gospel, 1965 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Department of State, 1961 (Box 21)
    - Valenzuela, Oscar G., 1985 (Box 21)
    - Van Horne, H. Norden, 1975 (Box 21)
    - Vargas, Jorge B., 1959-1960 (Box 21)
    - Verallo, Vermén M., 1978 (Box 21)
    - Verheye, Pierre, C. T., 1979 (Box 21)
    - Vetch, Henry, 1959-1971 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Viewing, Hermann, 1962; 1966-1968; undated (Box 21)
    - Villamor, Nanette M., 1960-1996 (with gaps) (Box 21)
    - Vinson, Benjamin, 1983-1986; undated (Box 21)
    - Viray, Manuel A., 1956-1962; 1985-1987; 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Vivian, Joyce, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
    - Vogelgesang, John, 1959-1960; 1972; 1983 (Box 21)
    - Volunteers of America-Michigan, 1960 (Box 21)
    - Von Neff, Erich V., 1980-1981; 1983-1985 (Box 21)
    - Von Peterffy, George A., 1983 (Box 21)
    - Wade, Ged, 1978-1979 (Box 21)
    - Waetke, Heinz, 1983-1984 (Box 21)
    - Walker, Janet, 1954-1964 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Wallace, Barbara and Donald, 1982-1983; undated (Box 21)
    - Walsh, Charles, 1957-1992 (scattered); undated (Box 21)
    - Wargo, Louis and Ellen, 1978; 1982-1984 (Box 21)
    - Warren, Irving and Bonnie, 1974-1984 (scattered); undated (Box 21)
    - Wayne State University, 1970-1982 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Weaver, William J., 1974 (Box 21)
    - Weightman, George, 1957-1958 (Box 21)
    - Weldy, Dwight E., 1973 (Box 21)
    - Welsh, Frank, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Werther, Evelyn, 1955; 1963-1964 (Box 21)
    - Weston, Hope, 1965-1987 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Westra, P. E., 1975 (Box 21)
    - Whinnom, Keith, 1957-1958 (Box 21)
    - Whitaker, Charles H., 1943-1944 (Box 21)
    - White, Lee A., 1944 (Box 21)
    - White, Michael, 1971 (Box 21)
    - White, R. R., 1971 (Box 21)
    - Whiting, Margaret, 1978-1985 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Whittaker, James A., 1983 (Box 21)
    - Wickberg, Edgar B. with gaps, 1957-1986; 6 folders (Box 21)
    - Wightman, E. H., 1978; 1985-1986 (Box 21)
    - Wightman, John, 1966; 1984; 1987 (Box 21)
    - Williams, Edward A., 1990 (Box 21)
    - Williams, J. David with gaps, 1971-1986; 4 folders (Box 21)
    - Williams, Ted R., 1980 (Box 21)
    - Wilson, Jo, 1979; 1986 (Box 21)
    - Wilson, Laurence L., 1956-1960 (Box 21)
    - Wilson, Richard C., 1958 (Box 21)
    - Wingo, Edna S., 1956; 1958-1960 (Box 21)
    - Winks, Wobin W., 1988 (Box 21)
    - Winslow, W. G., 1978 (Box 21)
    - Winter, Helmut, 1983 (Box 21)
    - Wisconsin, University of, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
    - Wisla, Ulla, 1940-1985 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Withee, Clara Somervile, 1948-1957 (scattered) (Box 21)
    - Wolfenden, Elmer P., 1967 (Box 21)
    - Wolfgang, Myra, 1970; 1975-1976 (Box 21)
    - Wolflisberg, Thomas, 1979 (Box 21)
    - World in Brief, Inc., 1962 (Box 21)
    - Wrigglesworth, Hazel, 1984-1991 (with gaps) (Box 22)
    - Wright, Joyce, 1970-1979 (scattered) (Box 22)
    - Wright, Timothy with gaps, 1972-1997; 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Yabes, Leopoldo Y., 1958-1960 (Box 22)
    - Yacano, Robert, 1996-1997 (Box 22)
    - Yale University Southeast Asia Studies, 1961-1962; 4 folders (Box 22)
    - Yoder, Margaret, 1970-1976 (Box 22)
    - Young, James W., 1986 (Box 22)
    - Young, Robert with gaps, 1951-2002; 7 folders (Box 22)
    - Zamora, Mario D., 1968-1974; 1977 (Box 22)
    - Zeitlin, Arnold, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Ziegler, John H. with gaps, 1966-1987; 7 folders (Box 22)
    - Zóbel, Fernando with gaps, 1957-1984; 2 folders (Box 22)
    - Zondek family, 1955-1976 (with gaps) (Box 22)
    - Zubal, John, 1981-1985 (scattered) (Box 22)
    - Anniversary correspondence, 1992 (Box 22)
    - Unidentified, 1941-1997 (scattered) (Box 22)
    - Correspondence arranged by date with gaps, 1948-1974; 6 folders (Box 22)
  - Cellar Book Shop records
    The Cellar Book Shop subseries includes annotated card catalog of titles on the Philippines Islands and South East Asia. Each card contains detailed bibliographic information, price(s), physical description including condition when necessary, number and types of illustrations and maps, presence of reference apparatus, and content summary by Mr. Netzorg. The catalog is valuable bibliographic resource in the area of South East Asian studies and publishing.
    - Philippine Islands card catalog
      - Integrated catalog A-F (Box 23)
      - Integrated catalog G-N (Box 24)
      - Integrated catalog O-Z (Box 25)
      - Journals (Box 25)
      - Linguistics (Box 25)
      - Pamphlets (Box 25)
      - Sold catalog, Phe-S (Box 25)
      - Sold catalog, T-Z (Box 26)
      - Untitled catalog (Box 26)
    - South East Asia card catalog
      - General catalog A-M (Box 27)
      - General Catalog N-Z (Box 28)
      - Sold catalog A (Box 28)
      - Sold catalog B-Coo (Box 29)
      - Sold catalog Cr-Guides (Box 30)
      - Sold catalog H-Ko (Box 31)
      - Sold catalog Kr-N (Box 32)
      - Sold Catalog Ni-Sm (Box 33)
      - Sold Catalog Sn-Z (Box 34)
- Visual material
  The Visual Material series includes photographs and slides of Fuld and Netzorg families. The majority of photographs depict family and friends, as wells as the Netzorgs' house in Detroit, Detroit street scenes, and of the Cellar Book Shop. Of special interest are the World War II period photographs in the Morton I. and Katherine S. Netzorg part of the series depicting the conditions in liberated Philippines in 1945, military action and military life, and Jewish life in the U.S. military. Also of interest are the Fuld family photographs depicting Jewish life in Germany from the late 1800s to late 1930s.
  Slides include images taken during 1970s trips to the Philippines featuring Banaue, Cebu, Jolo, and Zamboanga, locations in the South East Asia, and Europe.
  - Fuld family photographs
    - Fuld family, late, 1800s-1970s; undated (Box 35)
    - Family and friends, Germany, 1920-1930s (Box 35)
    - Frank family, 1941; undated (Box 35)
    - Photo albums, 1935-1936; 8 volumes (Box 35)
  - Netzorg family photographs
    - Family, late, 1800s-1940s; undated (Box 35)
    - World War II, 1945
      - Burials and cemeteries (Box 35)
      - Destruction, refugees and casualties (Box 35)
      - Morton I. Netzorg portraits (Box 35)
      - U.S. Military Forces (Box 35)
      - Jewish Welfare Board for Soldier’s and Sailor’s Relief
        - Club House (Box 35)
        - Committee for Presentation of Gift to Jewish People (Box 35)
        - Religious services (Box 35)
  - Morton J. and Petra Netzorg photographs
    - Portraits and family gatherings, 1940s-2000s (Box 35)
    - House in Detroit, 1950s-1990s (Box 35)
    - Cellar Book Shop, 1957-1999 (Box 35)
    - Conferences, 1980s (Box 35)
    - Detroit, 1960s-1970s; undated (Box 35)
    - Philippines
      - Friends, 1930-1940s; 1994 (Box 35)
    - Trips and reunions
      - Petra Fuld Netzorg’s trip of Asia and Israel, 1958 (Box 35)
      - Trips to the Philippines, 1976-1991 (Box 35)
  - Slides
    - Morton J. and Petra Fuld Netzorg trips, 1970s (Box 35)
  - Drawings
    - Morton J. Netzorg’s sketchbooks, 1973-1986; 5 volumes (Box 35)
    - Morton J. Netzorg’s drawings (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 35)
- Sound recordings
  The Sound Recordings series consists of cassette tapes with recorded reminiscences of Morton J. and Petra Netzorg.
  - Morton J. Netzorg oral history, 8 audiocassettes (Box 36)
  - Petra Netzog oral history, 7 audiocassettes (Box 36)
- Oversize Material
  The Oversize series includes materials of Fuld and Netzorg families, mostly from the 1930s and 1940s. Oversize Fuld family material includes newspaper articles in Hebrew about Bracha Fuld, as well as genealogical information and diplomas belonging to Fuld family members.
  Oversize Morton I. and Katherine S. Netzorg oversize material includes 1945-1946 issues of the National Jewish Welfare Board newspaper Sentinel with articles about Morton I. Netzorg and Jewish life in the U.S. military and miscellaneous oversize newspaper clippings and items, and a map showing "bandit" activity in the Philippines in 1944. Also included David L. Netzorg’s (Jock’s brother) Princeton University diploma.